<ecopedia priority="0" icon="Prevent_LegalAction">
  <section type="header">GENERAL</section>
  <section>
	  <b>(1.)</b> No Racist, Sexist, Bigoted, Hateful or Hurtful, Speed, Actions or communication. This is a happy, Friendly and Safe place for people to play. Respect it.
	  <b>(2.)</b> Profanity Filter Is OFF, This is a Mature Age Setting. If you are offended by the use of profanity, please leave.
	  <b>(3.)</b> We do not sell, or buy anything through the means of outside currency. Partaking/Posting Links to this kind of thing will result in a ban.
	  <b>(4.)</b> Land Claims. The world is huge! 4km<small>2</small>! there is heaps of room for you to setup! So give your neighbors some space! Minimum 3 Claim Spots apart. No Less. 
	  <b>(4.1)</b> Exception to this rule. If you are a in a group then this 3 Claim spot rule does not apply.
	  <b>(5.)</b> Botting, Second Accounts, Are NOT Allowed. Second Accounts and bots will be banned. Mains will not. We have an IP Logger that notifies us of Multiple people on the same network.
	  <b>(5.1)</b> Ignore Rule 5. Only IF, you and your partner/children play together, and you are in the same house.
	  <b>(6.)</b> Account Sharing. It's Dangerous and its not allowed here. Giving your account details to another person in the server can result in you losing your account completely.
	  <b>(7.)</b> No Spamming. This includes, Chat, PM, and in the forums. Spamming is not allowed. Please be respectful to other players.
	  <b>(8.)</b> No Advertising. This includes, Chat, PM, and in the forums. Advertising is not allowed. Please be respectful to other players.
	  <b>(8.1)</b> The only exception here is Mods, Feel Free to share your mods with us on the discord! We love seeing other mods! Who knows we may even add them to the server!
	  <b>(9.)</b> No Cheating. This includes, Hacks, Exploits, and Glitches. Cheating is not allowed.
	  <b>(10.)</b> No Griefing. This includes, Destroying other players property, and stealing from other players. Griefing is not allowed.
	  <b>(11.)</b> Admins Word, Is Law. Sorry, but someone has to step in and sort you people out. If you have a problem with an admin, please contact the owner.
  </section>

	<section type="header">Admins</section>
	<section>
		There is only 1 Admin, and thats me. Kye.
		The rest are just moderators,

		They can only kick people from the server and ban with permission, they don't have access to cheat commands such as give or anything else.

		Moderators also have access to a command called "TP Here" this allows them to teleport Troublesome players to their position, as well as those who may be stuck.

		Moderators also, like players, have access to the /tpr command (Teleport Request) this allows them to teleport to a player, but only if they have accepted the request. This is how they get around with admin abilities. so look out for the request!
	</section>

	<section type="header">Kye</section>
	<section>
		Kye Loves you all and is greatful for your support! But, he is really busy, so please be patient with him. He will get to you as soon as he can.
		
		He may appear randomly like a wild Ditto, Spawning in random items and checking them, testing them, seeing how broken things are.
		
		Kye is the only one with unrestricted admin abilities, but he owns the server, what can you do.
	</section>
</ecopedia>